{
  "uniqueId": "english definitions 3",
  "name": "English Vocabulary Quiz",
  "article": "an",
  "instructions": "Guess the word!",
  "questionCreationStrategy": "TEXT_WITH_HINT",
  "dictionaryLinkStrategy": "WEBSTER_ANSWER",
  "answerTimeLimitStrategy": "WITH_HINT",
  "cardPreprocessingStrategy": "BETTER_ENGLISH_DEFINITIONS",
  "discordFinalAnswerListElementStrategy": "ANSWER_ONLY",
  "scoreAnswerStrategy": "ONE_ANSWER_ONE_POINT",
  "additionalAnswerWaitStrategy": "JAPANESE_SETTINGS",
  "discordIntermediateAnswerListElementStrategy": "CORRECT_ANSWERS",
  "answerCompareStrategy": "STRICT",
  "cards": [
    {
      "question": "excited by sudden surprise or alarm and making a quick involuntary movement",
      "answer": "startled"
    },
    {
      "question": "drag loosely along a surface",
      "answer": "trail"
    },
    {
      "question": "the attribute or quality of being deep, strong, or intense",
      "answer": "depth"
    },
    {
      "question": "throw or hurl from the mound to the batter, as in baseball",
      "answer": "deliver"
    },
    {
      "question": "presaging good fortune",
      "answer": "fortunate"
    },
    {
      "question": "put into a bag",
      "answer": "bag"
    },
    {
      "question": "to show differences when compared",
      "answer": "contrast"
    },
    {
      "question": "of a color intermediate between red and blue  ",
      "answer": "purple"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of paying money  ",
      "answer": "payment"
    },
    {
      "question": "point out or draw attention to in protest or remonstrance",
      "answer": "represent"
    },
    {
      "question": "education or instruction in the fundamentals of a field of knowledge",
      "answer": "foundation"
    },
    {
      "question": "painful as if caused by a sharp instrument",
      "answer": "cutting"
    },
    {
      "question": "subject to electrical shocks  ",
      "answer": "shock"
    },
    {
      "question": "a suite of rooms usually on one floor of an apartment house  ",
      "answer": "apartment"
    },
    {
      "question": "meant or adapted for an occasion or use",
      "answer": "suitable"
    },
    {
      "question": "brought about or caused",
      "answer": "induced"
    },
    {
      "question": "a customer of a hotel or restaurant etc.  ",
      "answer": "guest"
    },
    {
      "question": "existing in something specified",
      "answer": "existing"
    },
    {
      "question": "the production of eggs (especially in birds)  ",
      "answer": "laying"
    },
    {
      "question": "indulging excessively",
      "answer": "heavily"
    },
    {
      "question": "an instrumentality needed for an undertaking or to perform a service  ",
      "answer": "equipment"
    },
    {
      "question": "easily perceived by the senses or grasped by the mind",
      "answer": "obvious"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by socially or conventionally acceptable morals",
      "answer": "respectable"
    },
    {
      "question": "inspiring admiration or approval",
      "answer": "admirable"
    },
    {
      "question": "cover or swamp with water  ",
      "answer": "flow"
    },
    {
      "question": "coat with a layer of metal",
      "answer": "plate"
    },
    {
      "question": "travelling about without any clear destination",
      "answer": "wandering"
    },
    {
      "question": "resulting from or employing derivation",
      "answer": "derivative"
    },
    {
      "question": "(especially of incident sound or light) bent or sent back",
      "answer": "reflected"
    },
    {
      "question": "work as a clerk, as in the legal business  ",
      "answer": "clerk"
    },
    {
      "question": "cheap paper made from wood pulp and used for printing newspapers",
      "answer": "newspaper"
    },
    {
      "question": "fill tightly with a material",
      "answer": "stuff"
    },
    {
      "question": "make tracks upon  ",
      "answer": "track"
    },
    {
      "question": "a flat-bottomed volcanic crater that was formed by an explosion",
      "answer": "maar"
    },
    {
      "question": "attack with or as if with a pickaxe of ice or rocky ground, for example",
      "answer": "pick"
    },
    {
      "question": "dregs consisting of solid particles (especially of coffee) that form a residue",
      "answer": "grounds"
    },
    {
      "question": "decorate with flags",
      "answer": "flag"
    },
    {
      "question": "protected by trademark or patent or copyright",
      "answer": "proprietary"
    },
    {
      "question": "an enclosure for animals (as chicken or livestock)  ",
      "answer": "yard"
    },
    {
      "question": "act as an assistant in a subordinate or supportive function  ",
      "answer": "assist"
    },
    {
      "question": "a male human offspring",
      "answer": "son"
    },
    {
      "question": "any art that invokes supernatural powers  ",
      "answer": "magic"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a solicitation or petition for something desired",
      "answer": "solicit"
    },
    {
      "question": "hold in suspicion",
      "answer": "suspect"
    },
    {
      "question": "displeasing to the senses",
      "answer": "ugly"
    },
    {
      "question": "successful or assured of success",
      "answer": "made"
    },
    {
      "question": "go on a campaign",
      "answer": "campaign"
    },
    {
      "question": "show certain properties when being rolled",
      "answer": "roll"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or concerning this or that",
      "answer": "thereof"
    },
    {
      "question": "set forth authoritatively as obligatory",
      "answer": "imposed"
    },
    {
      "question": "something that serves as evidence",
      "answer": "testimony"
    },
    {
      "question": "gratify",
      "answer": "feed"
    },
    {
      "question": "show approval or appreciation of",
      "answer": "recognize"
    },
    {
      "question": "expand or complete (a part in a piece of baroque music) by supplying the harmonies indicated in the figured bass  ",
      "answer": "realize"
    },
    {
      "question": "a male deer, especially an adult male red deer  ",
      "answer": "hart"
    },
    {
      "question": "fasten with a rope",
      "answer": "rope"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause to finish a relationship with somebody",
      "answer": "finish"
    },
    {
      "question": "set into a usually circular motion in order to mix or blend  ",
      "answer": "stirred"
    },
    {
      "question": "a search for an alternative that meets cognitive criteria",
      "answer": "pursuit"
    },
    {
      "question": "any recognized accomplishment",
      "answer": "performance"
    },
    {
      "question": "small in quantity",
      "answer": "slender"
    },
    {
      "question": "the social process whereby societies achieve an advanced stage of development and organization  ",
      "answer": "civilization"
    },
    {
      "question": "being a member of or formed into a labor union",
      "answer": "organized"
    },
    {
      "question": "be contingent upon (something that is elided)",
      "answer": "depend"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause to be returned",
      "answer": "recall"
    },
    {
      "question": "refuse to comply  ",
      "answer": "resist"
    },
    {
      "question": "show and train",
      "answer": "handle"
    },
    {
      "question": "closely similar or comparable in kind or quality or quantity or degree",
      "answer": "same"
    },
    {
      "question": "a task assigned for individual study",
      "answer": "lesson"
    },
    {
      "question": "to consider or examine in speech or writing",
      "answer": "discourse"
    },
    {
      "question": "render capable or able for some task",
      "answer": "enable"
    },
    {
      "question": "assign to a specific task",
      "answer": "detail"
    },
    {
      "question": "having a positive charge",
      "answer": "positive"
    },
    {
      "question": "not expected or anticipated",
      "answer": "unexpected"
    },
    {
      "question": "fill with tears or shed tears",
      "answer": "tear"
    },
    {
      "question": "a unit of length equal to one twelfth of a foot  ",
      "answer": "inch"
    },
    {
      "question": "a shelter from danger or hardship  ",
      "answer": "refuge"
    },
    {
      "question": "become limp",
      "answer": "wilt"
    },
    {
      "question": "judge tentatively or form an estimate of (quantities or time)",
      "answer": "estimate"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking strength",
      "answer": "feeble"
    },
    {
      "question": "warm compassionate feelings  ",
      "answer": "tenderness"
    },
    {
      "question": "incongruous;inviting ridicule",
      "answer": "absurd"
    },
    {
      "question": "acquisition of property by descent or by will  ",
      "answer": "succession"
    },
    {
      "question": "be on the mind of",
      "answer": "concern"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who is intoxicated  ",
      "answer": "drunk"
    },
    {
      "question": "make happy or satisfied  ",
      "answer": "satisfy"
    },
    {
      "question": "machine-readable text that is not sequential but is organized so that related items of information are connected",
      "answer": "hypertext"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of praying for divine protection  ",
      "answer": "blessing"
    },
    {
      "question": "by that means or because of that",
      "answer": "thereby"
    },
    {
      "question": "rid of objects or obstructions such as e.g. trees and brush",
      "answer": "cleared"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of meting out justice according to the law  ",
      "answer": "administration"
    },
    {
      "question": "being or affecting a disease produced by a particular microorganism or condition",
      "answer": "specific"
    },
    {
      "question": "a female member of a royal family other than the queen (especially the daughter of a sovereign)  ",
      "answer": "princess"
    },
    {
      "question": "neither too great nor too little",
      "answer": "indifferent"
    },
    {
      "question": "flattened laterally along the whole length (e.g., certain leafstalks or flatfishes)  ",
      "answer": "compressed"
    },
    {
      "question": "create by artistic means",
      "answer": "create"
    },
    {
      "question": "get high, stoned, or drugged",
      "answer": "trip"
    },
    {
      "question": "established by authority",
      "answer": "approved"
    },
    {
      "question": "undergo a test",
      "answer": "test"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of inflicting corporal punishment with repeated blows  ",
      "answer": "beating"
    },
    {
      "question": "a group of persons together in one place  ",
      "answer": "gathering"
    },
    {
      "question": "just as it should be",
      "answer": "precisely"
    },
    {
      "question": "disposed to bestow favors",
      "answer": "gracious"
    },
    {
      "question": "a collection of precious things",
      "answer": "treasure"
    },
    {
      "question": "a businessperson engaged in retail trade  ",
      "answer": "merchant"
    },
    {
      "question": "lower than a given reference point",
      "answer": "inferior"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by beauty of movement, style, form, or execution  ",
      "answer": "graceful"
    },
    {
      "question": "beat with a cat-o'-nine-tails  ",
      "answer": "cat"
    },
    {
      "question": "violent and excited activity",
      "answer": "fun"
    },
    {
      "question": "produce buds, branches, or germinate",
      "answer": "shoot"
    },
    {
      "question": "(computer science) written programs or procedures or rules and associated documentation pertaining to the operation of a computer system and that are stored in read/write memory",
      "answer": "software"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who is tricked or swindled  ",
      "answer": "victim"
    },
    {
      "question": "a professional person authorized to practice law",
      "answer": "lawyer"
    },
    {
      "question": "read for errors",
      "answer": "proofread"
    },
    {
      "question": "the proper or conventional behavior on some solemn occasion",
      "answer": "ceremony"
    },
    {
      "question": "become aware of not through the senses but instinctively",
      "answer": "smell"
    },
    {
      "question": "a means of exerting influence or gaining advantage",
      "answer": "purchase"
    },
    {
      "question": "having skin rich in melanin pigments",
      "answer": "colored"
    },
    {
      "question": "desert (a cause, a country or an army), often in order to join the opposing cause, country, or army",
      "answer": "defect"
    },
    {
      "question": "a raised structure on which gifts or sacrifices to a god are made  ",
      "answer": "altar"
    },
    {
      "question": "enveloped",
      "answer": "involved"
    },
    {
      "question": "the feeling that accompanies something extremely surprising",
      "answer": "astonishment"
    },
    {
      "question": "the commercial activity involved in repairing old structures or constructing new ones",
      "answer": "construction"
    },
    {
      "question": "take a liking to",
      "answer": "cotton"
    },
    {
      "question": "give a structure to",
      "answer": "structure"
    },
    {
      "question": "an agreement (or contract) in which property is transferred from the seller (vendor) to the buyer (vendee) for a fixed price in money (paid or agreed to be paid by the buyer)",
      "answer": "sale"
    },
    {
      "question": "at a short distance",
      "answer": "shortly"
    },
    {
      "question": "appealing to the general public",
      "answer": "favorite"
    },
    {
      "question": "call to mind",
      "answer": "suggest"
    },
    {
      "question": "transmit a title or property  ",
      "answer": "convey"
    },
    {
      "question": "lost in thought",
      "answer": "absent"
    },
    {
      "question": "the most important or necessary part of something",
      "answer": "basis"
    },
    {
      "question": "a personified abstraction that teaches",
      "answer": "teacher"
    },
    {
      "question": "involving or being or having the nature of a crime",
      "answer": "criminal"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of making something different (as e.g. the size of a garment)  ",
      "answer": "alteration"
    },
    {
      "question": "of a slope",
      "answer": "steep"
    },
    {
      "question": "a fractional monetary unit of Japan and Indonesia and Cambodia",
      "answer": "sen"
    },
    {
      "question": "large moth of temperate forests of Eurasia having heavily scaled transparent wings  ",
      "answer": "emperor"
    },
    {
      "question": "activity leading to skilled behavior  ",
      "answer": "training"
    },
    {
      "question": "of extreme beauty",
      "answer": "exquisite"
    },
    {
      "question": "provide a feast or banquet for  ",
      "answer": "feast"
    },
    {
      "question": "the condition of prospering",
      "answer": "prosperity"
    },
    {
      "question": "a feeling of righteous anger  ",
      "answer": "indignation"
    },
    {
      "question": "a wild and exciting undertaking (not necessarily lawful)  ",
      "answer": "adventure"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of giving someone a job  ",
      "answer": "employment"
    },
    {
      "question": "having or expressing strong emotions  ",
      "answer": "passionate"
    },
    {
      "question": "suspicious or unduly suspicious or fearful of being displaced by a rival",
      "answer": "jealous"
    },
    {
      "question": "pleasantly new or different",
      "answer": "novel"
    },
    {
      "question": "hold back",
      "answer": "conceal"
    },
    {
      "question": "a word used for misbehaving children",
      "answer": "silly"
    },
    {
      "question": "tolerating without protest",
      "answer": "accepting"
    },
    {
      "question": "having or displaying great dignity or nobility",
      "answer": "gallant"
    },
    {
      "question": "communication between individuals  ",
      "answer": "intercourse"
    },
    {
      "question": "with unusual distress or resentment or regret or emotional display",
      "answer": "badly"
    },
    {
      "question": "behavior intended to please your parents",
      "answer": "obedience"
    },
    {
      "question": "readiness to embark on bold new ventures  ",
      "answer": "enterprise"
    },
    {
      "question": "a feeling of intense anger",
      "answer": "fury"
    },
    {
      "question": "a garment size for a large or heavy person  ",
      "answer": "stout"
    },
    {
      "question": "being the agent or cause",
      "answer": "responsible"
    },
    {
      "question": "go or travel along with",
      "answer": "accompany"
    },
    {
      "question": "ask (someone) to marry you",
      "answer": "propose"
    },
    {
      "question": "(plural) the lay members of a male religious order  ",
      "answer": "brethren"
    },
    {
      "question": "take up someone's soul into heaven",
      "answer": "assume"
    },
    {
      "question": "be or become preserved",
      "answer": "cure"
    },
    {
      "question": "an unfortunate state resulting from unfavorable outcomes  ",
      "answer": "misfortune"
    },
    {
      "question": "the period of time during which a place or position or nation is occupied",
      "answer": "occupation"
    },
    {
      "question": "bestow a privilege upon  ",
      "answer": "privilege"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of robbing a helpless person",
      "answer": "rolling"
    },
    {
      "question": "absence of affectation or pretense  ",
      "answer": "simplicity"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of e.g. celestial bodies) above the horizon",
      "answer": "risen"
    },
    {
      "question": "deciding or controlling something's outcome or nature",
      "answer": "determination"
    },
    {
      "question": "of agriculture",
      "answer": "extensive"
    },
    {
      "question": "firmly closed or secured",
      "answer": "fastened"
    },
    {
      "question": "size or measure according to a scale",
      "answer": "scale"
    },
    {
      "question": "provide or equip with furniture",
      "answer": "furnish"
    },
    {
      "question": "(often used with `pay') a formal expression of esteem",
      "answer": "respects"
    },
    {
      "question": "having passed out of existence",
      "answer": "vanished"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being valueless or futile",
      "answer": "vanity"
    },
    {
      "question": "unsolicited and resisted by the management of the target company ( used of attempts to buy or take control of a business)",
      "answer": "hostile"
    },
    {
      "question": "be in equilibrium",
      "answer": "balance"
    },
    {
      "question": "unsettled in mind or opinion",
      "answer": "doubtful"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause to take roots  ",
      "answer": "root"
    },
    {
      "question": "emit a brief burst of light",
      "answer": "flash"
    },
    {
      "question": "to proceed quickly and easily  ",
      "answer": "breeze"
    },
    {
      "question": "a collection of facts from which conclusions may be drawn",
      "answer": "data"
    },
    {
      "question": "a form of trustworthiness",
      "answer": "responsibility"
    },
    {
      "question": "regulate or set the pace of",
      "answer": "pace"
    },
    {
      "question": "excessive fervor to do something or accomplish some end",
      "answer": "zeal"
    },
    {
      "question": "be the rival of, be in competition with",
      "answer": "rival"
    },
    {
      "question": "yield to another's wish or opinion",
      "answer": "submit"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an original manner  ",
      "answer": "originally"
    },
    {
      "question": "work occasionally",
      "answer": "job"
    },
    {
      "question": "as if dead  ",
      "answer": "deadly"
    },
    {
      "question": "a woman participant in her own marriage ceremony  ",
      "answer": "bride"
    },
    {
      "question": "a new proposal",
      "answer": "introduction"
    },
    {
      "question": "a systematic investigation of a matter of public interest  ",
      "answer": "inquiry"
    },
    {
      "question": "the successful ending of the American Revolution",
      "answer": "independence"
    },
    {
      "question": "something done as an indication of intention",
      "answer": "gesture"
    },
    {
      "question": "without conscious volition  ",
      "answer": "unconscious"
    },
    {
      "question": "not much",
      "answer": "little"
    },
    {
      "question": "a special loved one  ",
      "answer": "darling"
    },
    {
      "question": "open and genuine",
      "answer": "sincere"
    },
    {
      "question": "the business of issuing printed matter for sale or distribution  ",
      "answer": "publication"
    },
    {
      "question": "giving pleasure and satisfaction",
      "answer": "pleasing"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to or characteristic of regions of eastern parts of the world",
      "answer": "eastern"
    },
    {
      "question": "a learner who is enrolled in an educational institution  ",
      "answer": "student"
    },
    {
      "question": "qualities that are comparable",
      "answer": "comparison"
    },
    {
      "question": "pass out of one's memory  ",
      "answer": "slip"
    },
    {
      "question": "belonging to or characteristic of Romanticism or the Romantic Movement in the arts",
      "answer": "romantic"
    },
    {
      "question": "a tempting allurement",
      "answer": "invitation"
    },
    {
      "question": "a commissioned naval officer who ranks above a lieutenant commander and below a captain  ",
      "answer": "commander"
    },
    {
      "question": "box with a lid",
      "answer": "chest"
    },
    {
      "question": "to obscure, or conceal with or as if with a veil",
      "answer": "veil"
    },
    {
      "question": "cut teeth into",
      "answer": "jag"
    },
    {
      "question": "the group action of a collection of people or animals or vehicles moving ahead in more or less regular formation",
      "answer": "procession"
    },
    {
      "question": "purely outward or superficial",
      "answer": "external"
    },
    {
      "question": "an unsuccessful ending to a struggle or contest",
      "answer": "defeat"
    },
    {
      "question": "a nobleman (in various countries) of high rank  ",
      "answer": "duke"
    },
    {
      "question": "prolonged unfulfilled desire or need  ",
      "answer": "longing"
    },
    {
      "question": "compelling immediate action",
      "answer": "pressing"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by or constituting a form of government in which power is divided between one central and several regional authorities",
      "answer": "federal"
    },
    {
      "question": "being one more than fifteen  ",
      "answer": "sixteen"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of taking revenge (harming someone in retaliation for something harmful that they have done) especially in the next life",
      "answer": "vengeance"
    },
    {
      "question": "take account of",
      "answer": "reckon"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a swift manner",
      "answer": "swiftly"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of protecting something by covering it  ",
      "answer": "covering"
    },
    {
      "question": "paint (a surface) to make it look like stone or wood  ",
      "answer": "grain"
    },
    {
      "question": "made or joined or united into one  ",
      "answer": "combined"
    },
    {
      "question": "gather into a club-like mass",
      "answer": "club"
    },
    {
      "question": "retained without reflection",
      "answer": "absorbed"
    },
    {
      "question": "string on a wire",
      "answer": "wire"
    },
    {
      "question": "the melody carried by a particular voice or instrument in polyphonic music",
      "answer": "part"
    },
    {
      "question": "a state of widespread public excitement and interest",
      "answer": "sensation"
    },
    {
      "question": "a defendant in a criminal proceeding  ",
      "answer": "accused"
    },
    {
      "question": "in or to another place",
      "answer": "elsewhere"
    },
    {
      "question": "go against, as of rules and laws",
      "answer": "conflict"
    },
    {
      "question": "not disturbed by strife or turmoil or war",
      "answer": "peaceful"
    },
    {
      "question": "being one more than thirteen  ",
      "answer": "fourteen"
    },
    {
      "question": "strong and active physically or mentally",
      "answer": "vigorous"
    },
    {
      "question": "hold dear",
      "answer": "prize"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking or marked by lack of intellectual acuity  ",
      "answer": "stupid"
    },
    {
      "question": "take away or remove",
      "answer": "fetch"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of making something perfect  ",
      "answer": "perfection"
    },
    {
      "question": "unpleasantly stormy",
      "answer": "dirty"
    },
    {
      "question": "an adornment that hangs from a piece of jewelry (necklace or earring)  ",
      "answer": "pendant"
    },
    {
      "question": "generally accepted  ",
      "answer": "acknowledged"
    },
    {
      "question": "money collected under a tariff  ",
      "answer": "customs"
    },
    {
      "question": "unable to manage independently",
      "answer": "helpless"
    },
    {
      "question": "speak softly",
      "answer": "whisper"
    },
    {
      "question": "wish harm upon",
      "answer": "curse"
    },
    {
      "question": "at or in an indicated (usually distant) place (`yon' is archaic and dialectal)",
      "answer": "yonder"
    },
    {
      "question": "regarded with admiration  ",
      "answer": "admired"
    },
    {
      "question": "toward the outside",
      "answer": "outward"
    },
    {
      "question": "communication by the exchange of letters  ",
      "answer": "correspondence"
    },
    {
      "question": "the head administrative officer of a college or university  ",
      "answer": "president"
    },
    {
      "question": "go along the rim, like a beard around the chin",
      "answer": "beard"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to or characteristic of or being a member of the traditional racial division of mankind having brown to black pigmentation and tightly curled hair  ",
      "answer": "negro"
    },
    {
      "question": "line that is the commercial organization responsible for operating a system of transportation for trains that pull passengers or freight  ",
      "answer": "railway"
    },
    {
      "question": "a symbol of commercialism or greed",
      "answer": "dollar"
    },
    {
      "question": "characteristic of or resembling or accompanied by music",
      "answer": "musical"
    },
    {
      "question": "construct a model of",
      "answer": "model"
    },
    {
      "question": "of low or inferior quality or value",
      "answer": "coarse"
    },
    {
      "question": "moderate in type or degree or effect or force",
      "answer": "mild"
    },
    {
      "question": "not in a forthright manner",
      "answer": "indirectly"
    },
    {
      "question": "wet as from washing",
      "answer": "washed"
    },
    {
      "question": "hold firmly  ",
      "answer": "grasp"
    },
    {
      "question": "something that is created by arranging several things to form a unified whole",
      "answer": "composition"
    },
    {
      "question": "not offensive to sexual mores in conduct or appearance  ",
      "answer": "modest"
    },
    {
      "question": "pleasantly occupied",
      "answer": "amused"
    },
    {
      "question": "(baseball) a relief pitcher who can protect a lead in the last inning or two of the game  ",
      "answer": "closer"
    },
    {
      "question": "an agreeable sound property  ",
      "answer": "harmony"
    },
    {
      "question": "design or destine",
      "answer": "intend"
    },
    {
      "question": "become filled to overflowing",
      "answer": "flood"
    },
    {
      "question": "use as a basis for",
      "answer": "establish"
    },
    {
      "question": "mentally confused",
      "answer": "confused"
    },
    {
      "question": "act of receiving pleasure from something  ",
      "answer": "enjoyment"
    },
    {
      "question": "convert grain into flour  ",
      "answer": "flour"
    },
    {
      "question": "large migratory American butterfly having deep orange wings with black and white markings",
      "answer": "monarch"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who carries a message  ",
      "answer": "messenger"
    },
    {
      "question": "an inherited pattern of thought or action  ",
      "answer": "tradition"
    },
    {
      "question": "a wide scarf worn about their shoulders by women  ",
      "answer": "stole"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who possesses unusual innate ability in some field or activity  ",
      "answer": "talent"
    },
    {
      "question": "having received information",
      "answer": "advised"
    },
    {
      "question": "consisting of or characterized by the telling of a story",
      "answer": "narrative"
    },
    {
      "question": "the state of being excluded  ",
      "answer": "exclusion"
    },
    {
      "question": "treat gingerly or carefully",
      "answer": "stroke"
    },
    {
      "question": "punish in order to gain control or enforce obedience",
      "answer": "discipline"
    },
    {
      "question": "plaster with mud  ",
      "answer": "mud"
    },
    {
      "question": "to make or produce a loud noise",
      "answer": "thunder"
    },
    {
      "question": "tolerant of change",
      "answer": "liberal"
    },
    {
      "question": "break down and crush by beating, as with a pestle",
      "answer": "pound"
    },
    {
      "question": "an article of merchandise that is displayed or advertised more than other articles  ",
      "answer": "feature"
    },
    {
      "question": "hold under a lease or rental agreement",
      "answer": "rent"
    },
    {
      "question": "drop a hint",
      "answer": "hint"
    },
    {
      "question": "the grammatical relation that exists when a word qualifies the meaning of the phrase  ",
      "answer": "modification"
    },
    {
      "question": "an institution set up to provide help to the needy  ",
      "answer": "charity"
    },
    {
      "question": "(law) the act of disposing of property by virtue of the power of appointment",
      "answer": "appointment"
    },
    {
      "question": "remove the ovaries of",
      "answer": "alter"
    },
    {
      "question": "become pregnant",
      "answer": "conceive"
    },
    {
      "question": "attack with gas",
      "answer": "gas"
    },
    {
      "question": "a self-constituted organization to promote something  ",
      "answer": "committee"
    },
    {
      "question": "cover with a sheet, as if by wrapping",
      "answer": "sheet"
    },
    {
      "question": "a native or naturalized member of a state or other political community  ",
      "answer": "citizen"
    },
    {
      "question": "set in the soil for growth  ",
      "answer": "planted"
    },
    {
      "question": "appropriate to the beginning or start of an event",
      "answer": "starting"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking a caretaker",
      "answer": "neglected"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who operates a farm  ",
      "answer": "farmer"
    },
    {
      "question": "cover with or as if with a cloak",
      "answer": "cloak"
    },
    {
      "question": "zealous vigilance",
      "answer": "jealousy"
    },
    {
      "question": "(computer science) a line of code written as part of a computer program  ",
      "answer": "instruction"
    },
    {
      "question": "the condition of belonging to a particular place or group by virtue of social or ethnic or cultural lineage",
      "answer": "roots"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or created by one without formal training",
      "answer": "primitive"
    },
    {
      "question": "as follows  ",
      "answer": "namely"
    },
    {
      "question": "for someone's benefit (usually expressed as `in behalf' rather than `on behalf' and usually with a possessive)",
      "answer": "behalf"
    },
    {
      "question": "measure the time or duration of an event or action or the person who performs an action in a certain period of time",
      "answer": "clock"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a tour of a certain place",
      "answer": "tour"
    },
    {
      "question": "arrange for and reserve (something for someone else) in advance",
      "answer": "reserve"
    },
    {
      "question": "the overthrow of a government by those who are governed  ",
      "answer": "revolution"
    },
    {
      "question": "suggest sex to",
      "answer": "proposition"
    },
    {
      "question": "arrange thoughts, ideas, temporal events",
      "answer": "arrange"
    },
    {
      "question": "(chemistry) a substance consisting of two or more substances mixed together (not in fixed proportions and not with chemical bonding)  ",
      "answer": "mixture"
    },
    {
      "question": "get a certain number or letter indicating quality or performance",
      "answer": "score"
    },
    {
      "question": "a desk used for writing  ",
      "answer": "secretary"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of sharing in the activities of a group",
      "answer": "engagement"
    },
    {
      "question": "enclosed securely in a covering of paper or the like",
      "answer": "wrapped"
    },
    {
      "question": "an atmosphere of depression and melancholy",
      "answer": "gloom"
    },
    {
      "question": "the extent of a 2-dimensional surface enclosed within a boundary",
      "answer": "area"
    },
    {
      "question": "experience a feeling of well-being or happiness, as from good health or an intense emotion",
      "answer": "glow"
    },
    {
      "question": "(used of tobacco) aging as a preservative process (`aged' is pronounced as one syllable)  ",
      "answer": "aged"
    },
    {
      "question": "harmed or injured or spoiled",
      "answer": "damaged"
    },
    {
      "question": "take revenge for a perceived wrong",
      "answer": "revenge"
    },
    {
      "question": "that is to say",
      "answer": "i.e."
    },
    {
      "question": "effortless and unstudied",
      "answer": "careless"
    },
    {
      "question": "without moving or making a sound",
      "answer": "still"
    },
    {
      "question": "an open skin infection  ",
      "answer": "sore"
    },
    {
      "question": "being one more than one",
      "answer": "two"
    },
    {
      "question": "a blunder that makes you look ridiculous",
      "answer": "spectacle"
    },
    {
      "question": "without doubt",
      "answer": "undoubtedly"
    },
    {
      "question": "a state of acute pain  ",
      "answer": "agony"
    },
    {
      "question": "suited to your comfort or purpose or needs",
      "answer": "convenient"
    },
    {
      "question": "clearly and explicitly stated",
      "answer": "specified"
    },
    {
      "question": "act as an informer",
      "answer": "inform"
    },
    {
      "question": "a party of people at a wedding  ",
      "answer": "wedding"
    },
    {
      "question": "affect",
      "answer": "seize"
    },
    {
      "question": "ambiguous (especially in the negative)",
      "answer": "uncertain"
    },
    {
      "question": "having or showing or expressing reverence for a deity",
      "answer": "pious"
    },
    {
      "question": "freedom to choose a pastime or enjoyable activity",
      "answer": "leisure"
    },
    {
      "question": "(American football) the act of catching a pass in football",
      "answer": "reception"
    },
    {
      "question": "any tubular or pillar-like supporting structure in the body  ",
      "answer": "column"
    },
    {
      "question": "having or displaying warmth or affection",
      "answer": "affectionate"
    },
    {
      "question": "transport by railroad  ",
      "answer": "railroad"
    },
    {
      "question": "a recompense for worthy acts or retribution for wrongdoing",
      "answer": "wages"
    },
    {
      "question": "marked by avoidance of extravagance or extremes",
      "answer": "moderate"
    },
    {
      "question": "unbiased impartial unconcern  ",
      "answer": "indifference"
    },
    {
      "question": "give little or no attention to",
      "answer": "neglect"
    },
    {
      "question": "not equal in amount",
      "answer": "unlike"
    },
    {
      "question": "suffer spiritual death",
      "answer": "die"
    },
    {
      "question": "laugh unrestrainedly and heartily  ",
      "answer": "roar"
    },
    {
      "question": "tan (a skin) with bark tannins  ",
      "answer": "bark"
    },
    {
      "question": "store in bins  ",
      "answer": "bin"
    },
    {
      "question": "thrust down or into",
      "answer": "dig"
    },
    {
      "question": "meeting requirements",
      "answer": "satisfactory"
    },
    {
      "question": "consider to be equal or the same",
      "answer": "identify"
    },
    {
      "question": "shaped or conditioned or disciplined by training",
      "answer": "trained"
    },
    {
      "question": "the social act of assembling",
      "answer": "assembly"
    },
    {
      "question": "move along on or as if on wheels or a wheeled vehicle",
      "answer": "wheel"
    },
    {
      "question": "any military structure or vehicle bearing weapons  ",
      "answer": "platform"
    },
    {
      "question": "make aware of",
      "answer": "wake"
    },
    {
      "question": "financially rewarding",
      "answer": "economic"
    },
    {
      "question": "a British term for some kinds of insurance  ",
      "answer": "assurance"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of persons) freed from or not subject to an obligation or liability (as e.g. taxes) to which others or other things are subject",
      "answer": "exempt"
    },
    {
      "question": "wrongdoing that violates another's rights and is unjustly inflicted  ",
      "answer": "injury"
    },
    {
      "question": "toward or on the left",
      "answer": "left"
    },
    {
      "question": "regard with feelings of respect and reverence",
      "answer": "reverence"
    },
    {
      "question": "requiring or amenable to treatment by medicine especially as opposed to surgery",
      "answer": "medical"
    },
    {
      "question": "a ceremony at which a dead person is buried or cremated",
      "answer": "funeral"
    },
    {
      "question": "bring back into original existence, use, function, or position",
      "answer": "restore"
    },
    {
      "question": "(microbiology) a group of organisms grown from a single parent cell  ",
      "answer": "colony"
    },
    {
      "question": "(law) a procedure whereby a party to a suit says that a particular line of questioning or a particular witness or a piece of evidence or other matter is improper and should not be continued and asks the court to rule on its impropriety or illegality  ",
      "answer": "objection"
    },
    {
      "question": "not this merely but also",
      "answer": "nay"
    },
    {
      "question": "a covering designed to be worn on a person's body  ",
      "answer": "clothing"
    },
    {
      "question": "put forward a claim and assert right or possession of",
      "answer": "pretend"
    },
    {
      "question": "(music) a note that produces a dissonant chord is first heard in a consonant chord",
      "answer": "preparation"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by full comprehension of the problem involved",
      "answer": "educated"
    },
    {
      "question": "activity characterized by good humor  ",
      "answer": "jest"
    },
    {
      "question": "manifesting or characteristic of life",
      "answer": "vital"
    },
    {
      "question": "be worthy or deserving",
      "answer": "deserve"
    },
    {
      "question": "a commissioned military officer in the United States Army or Air Force or Marines who ranks above a lieutenant colonel and below a brigadier general  ",
      "answer": "colonel"
    },
    {
      "question": "(psychoanalysis) primitive instincts and energies underlying all psychic activity  ",
      "answer": "id"
    },
    {
      "question": "attractive especially by means of smallness or prettiness or quaintness",
      "answer": "cunning"
    },
    {
      "question": "drama in which the protagonist is overcome by some superior force or circumstance",
      "answer": "tragedy"
    },
    {
      "question": "a feeling of delight at being entertained  ",
      "answer": "amusement"
    },
    {
      "question": "logically deductive",
      "answer": "formal"
    },
    {
      "question": "the state of a child between infancy and adolescence  ",
      "answer": "childhood"
    },
    {
      "question": "of a light shade of red  ",
      "answer": "pink"
    },
    {
      "question": "a piece of furniture with a writing surface and usually drawers or other compartments  ",
      "answer": "desk"
    },
    {
      "question": "restless or short-tempered under delay or opposition",
      "answer": "impatient"
    },
    {
      "question": "load or burden",
      "answer": "saddle"
    },
    {
      "question": "no longer in the natural state",
      "answer": "cultivated"
    },
    {
      "question": "feel the need to eat  ",
      "answer": "hunger"
    },
    {
      "question": "specifically design a product, event, or activity for a certain public  ",
      "answer": "calculate"
    },
    {
      "question": "the successful action of solving a problem",
      "answer": "solution"
    },
    {
      "question": "occurring within an institution or community",
      "answer": "internal"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking or not affording physical or mental rest",
      "answer": "restless"
    },
    {
      "question": "having an owner",
      "answer": "owned"
    },
    {
      "question": "the local subdivision of a diocese committed to one pastor  ",
      "answer": "parish"
    },
    {
      "question": "the financial gain (earned or unearned) accruing over a given period of time  ",
      "answer": "income"
    },
    {
      "question": "achieved or reached",
      "answer": "attained"
    },
    {
      "question": "give dinner to",
      "answer": "dine"
    },
    {
      "question": "be a distinctive feature, attribute, or trait",
      "answer": "distinguish"
    },
    {
      "question": "a written evaluation of a work of literature  ",
      "answer": "criticism"
    },
    {
      "question": "coming into conflict with  ",
      "answer": "dispute"
    },
    {
      "question": "invariably occurring or appearing",
      "answer": "inevitable"
    },
    {
      "question": "not yet finished",
      "answer": "incomplete"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or belonging to or characteristic of this earth as distinguished from heaven",
      "answer": "earthly"
    },
    {
      "question": "gather nests  ",
      "answer": "nest"
    },
    {
      "question": "go away or leave  ",
      "answer": "depart"
    },
    {
      "question": "passing or able to pass air in and out of the lungs normally",
      "answer": "breathing"
    },
    {
      "question": "engaged in a struggle to overcome especially poverty or obscurity",
      "answer": "struggling"
    },
    {
      "question": "grow in a special preparation",
      "answer": "culture"
    },
    {
      "question": "tell romantic or exaggerated lies",
      "answer": "romance"
    },
    {
      "question": "preserve in a can or tin",
      "answer": "can"
    },
    {
      "question": "an army unit that uses big guns  ",
      "answer": "artillery"
    },
    {
      "question": "inspiring fear",
      "answer": "formidable"
    },
    {
      "question": "changing suddenly in direction and degree",
      "answer": "sharply"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause somebody to adopt a certain position, belief, or course of action",
      "answer": "persuade"
    },
    {
      "question": "cover with metal  ",
      "answer": "metal"
    },
    {
      "question": "used of a height or viewpoint",
      "answer": "commanding"
    },
    {
      "question": "used of a singer or singing voice that is marked by power and expressiveness and a histrionic or theatrical style",
      "answer": "dramatic"
    },
    {
      "question": "a garment size for short or slender women  ",
      "answer": "petite"
    },
    {
      "question": "produce leaves, of plants  ",
      "answer": "leaf"
    },
    {
      "question": "an act (or failure to act) that disappoints someone  ",
      "answer": "disappointment"
    },
    {
      "question": "housing that someone is living in",
      "answer": "dwelling"
    },
    {
      "question": "a medical institution where sick or injured people are given medical or surgical care  ",
      "answer": "hospital"
    },
    {
      "question": "(law) the institution of a sequence of steps by which legal judgments are invoked  ",
      "answer": "proceeding"
    },
    {
      "question": "baffled",
      "answer": "stuck"
    },
    {
      "question": "utter a sudden loud cry",
      "answer": "shout"
    },
    {
      "question": "apply a liquid to",
      "answer": "paint"
    },
    {
      "question": "preserved by removing natural moisture",
      "answer": "dried"
    },
    {
      "question": "fairly large",
      "answer": "ample"
    },
    {
      "question": "look at with admiration  ",
      "answer": "admire"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who visits  ",
      "answer": "visitor"
    },
    {
      "question": "experiencing a sudden sense of danger  ",
      "answer": "alarmed"
    },
    {
      "question": "in accordance with moral or social standards",
      "answer": "justly"
    },
    {
      "question": "unmistakably (`plain' is often used informally for `plainly')",
      "answer": "obviously"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of uniform movement  ",
      "answer": "translation"
    },
    {
      "question": "explore natural caves  ",
      "answer": "cave"
    },
    {
      "question": "devise the sequence of events in (a literary work or a play, movie, or ballet)",
      "answer": "plot"
    },
    {
      "question": "being or characteristic of government by representation in which citizens exercise power through elected officers and representatives",
      "answer": "representative"
    },
    {
      "question": "a specialized sphere of knowledge",
      "answer": "department"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a stringent manner",
      "answer": "strictly"
    },
    {
      "question": "accept (someone) to be what is claimed or accept his power and authority",
      "answer": "acknowledge"
    },
    {
      "question": "a celebrity who is lionized (much sought after)  ",
      "answer": "lion"
    },
    {
      "question": "broken away from sameness or identity or duplication",
      "answer": "varied"
    },
    {
      "question": "equal in amount or value",
      "answer": "like"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or belonging to heaven or god  ",
      "answer": "heavenly"
    },
    {
      "question": "the action of an armed force that surrounds a fortified place and isolates it while continuing to attack  ",
      "answer": "siege"
    },
    {
      "question": "restored to a new condition",
      "answer": "renewed"
    },
    {
      "question": "the wing of a fowl",
      "answer": "wing"
    },
    {
      "question": "engaged in by members of a profession",
      "answer": "professional"
    },
    {
      "question": "cook something by letting steam pass over it",
      "answer": "steam"
    },
    {
      "question": "of size and dignity suggestive of a statue  ",
      "answer": "stately"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by thriftiness",
      "answer": "saving"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause to be directed or transmitted to another place",
      "answer": "mail"
    },
    {
      "question": "final or ending",
      "answer": "closing"
    },
    {
      "question": "at once (usually modifies an undesirable occurrence)",
      "answer": "promptly"
    },
    {
      "question": "sell cheaply as remainders",
      "answer": "remainder"
    },
    {
      "question": "fill to overflow",
      "answer": "heap"
    },
    {
      "question": "(card games) in a single round, the sequence of cards played by all the players",
      "answer": "trick"
    },
    {
      "question": "spray finely or cover with mist  ",
      "answer": "mist"
    },
    {
      "question": "an activity that stands as an equivalent of something or results in an equivalent  ",
      "answer": "representation"
    },
    {
      "question": "examine eggs for freshness by holding them against a light  ",
      "answer": "candle"
    },
    {
      "question": "catch a glimpse of or see briefly",
      "answer": "glimpse"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of departing politely",
      "answer": "farewell"
    },
    {
      "question": "not drawing attention",
      "answer": "obscure"
    },
    {
      "question": "apply powder to",
      "answer": "powder"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of having a moderate degree of heat",
      "answer": "warmth"
    },
    {
      "question": "ready for service",
      "answer": "effective"
    },
    {
      "question": "the occupation of a house painter",
      "answer": "painting"
    },
    {
      "question": "the flash of light that accompanies an electric discharge in the atmosphere (or something resembling such a flash)",
      "answer": "lightning"
    },
    {
      "question": "relinquish possession or control over",
      "answer": "surrender"
    },
    {
      "question": "a solitary place  ",
      "answer": "solitude"
    },
    {
      "question": "require to be in a certain grammatical case, voice, or mood",
      "answer": "govern"
    },
    {
      "question": "raise oneself while hanging from one's hands until one's chin is level with the support bar  ",
      "answer": "chin"
    },
    {
      "question": "remove from its shell or outer covering",
      "answer": "shell"
    },
    {
      "question": "use a name to designate",
      "answer": "refer"
    },
    {
      "question": "following in time or order",
      "answer": "subsequent"
    },
    {
      "question": "to cleanse (itself or another animal) by licking",
      "answer": "wash"
    },
    {
      "question": "cover anew",
      "answer": "recover"
    },
    {
      "question": "administer poison to",
      "answer": "poison"
    },
    {
      "question": "an imaginary figure of superhuman size and strength",
      "answer": "giant"
    },
    {
      "question": "not meeting requirements",
      "answer": "incapable"
    },
    {
      "question": "aromatic annual or perennial herbs and shrubs  ",
      "answer": "tobacco"
    },
    {
      "question": "moving forward  ",
      "answer": "advancing"
    },
    {
      "question": "a personal enemy",
      "answer": "foe"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a willing manner",
      "answer": "gladly"
    },
    {
      "question": "the point on a curve where the tangent changes from positive on the left to negative on the right  ",
      "answer": "maximum"
    },
    {
      "question": "marked by deprivation especially of the necessities of life or healthful environmental influences",
      "answer": "deprived"
    },
    {
      "question": "not to be placated or appeased or moved by entreaty",
      "answer": "grim"
    },
    {
      "question": "place or lay as if in a pile",
      "answer": "pile"
    },
    {
      "question": "guarded from injury or destruction  ",
      "answer": "protected"
    },
    {
      "question": "a sculpture representing a human or animal  ",
      "answer": "statue"
    },
    {
      "question": "transfer a file or program from a central computer to a smaller computer or to a computer at a remote location  ",
      "answer": "download"
    },
    {
      "question": "a wooden block built into a masonry wall so that joinery structure can be nailed to it  ",
      "answer": "nog"
    },
    {
      "question": "light during the daytime  ",
      "answer": "daylight"
    },
    {
      "question": "temporary military shelter  ",
      "answer": "hut"
    },
    {
      "question": "carry further or advance",
      "answer": "pursue"
    },
    {
      "question": "those in charge of running a business  ",
      "answer": "management"
    },
    {
      "question": "capture as if by hunting, snaring, or trapping",
      "answer": "capture"
    },
    {
      "question": "appointed to a post or duty",
      "answer": "assigned"
    },
    {
      "question": "having or displaying qualities appropriate for heroes",
      "answer": "heroic"
    },
    {
      "question": "the prevailing psychological state",
      "answer": "climate"
    },
    {
      "question": "bring into a given condition by mental preoccupation",
      "answer": "think"
    },
    {
      "question": "reckless or malicious behavior that causes discomfort or annoyance in others  ",
      "answer": "mischief"
    },
    {
      "question": "make concave",
      "answer": "dish"
    },
    {
      "question": "(formal) in or into that thing or place",
      "answer": "therein"
    },
    {
      "question": "take in coal",
      "answer": "coal"
    },
    {
      "question": "suggestive of youth",
      "answer": "youthful"
    },
    {
      "question": "a consequence of someone's efforts or of a particular set of circumstances",
      "answer": "product"
    },
    {
      "question": "the action of prohibiting or inhibiting or forbidding (or an instance thereof)",
      "answer": "prohibition"
    },
    {
      "question": "reach the summit (of a mountain)",
      "answer": "summit"
    },
    {
      "question": "not openly",
      "answer": "secretly"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person responsible for the editorial aspects of publication",
      "answer": "editor"
    },
    {
      "question": "a bewildering profusion",
      "answer": "wilderness"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an open way",
      "answer": "openly"
    },
    {
      "question": "exercising or showing good judgment",
      "answer": "healthy"
    },
    {
      "question": "a specific form of evildoing",
      "answer": "vice"
    },
    {
      "question": "station (troops) in a fort or garrison  ",
      "answer": "garrison"
    },
    {
      "question": "impairment of normal physiological function affecting part or all of an organism  ",
      "answer": "illness"
    },
    {
      "question": "the great circle on the celestial sphere whose plane passes through the sensible horizon and the center of the Earth  ",
      "answer": "horizon"
    },
    {
      "question": "marked by self-restraint and reticence",
      "answer": "reserved"
    },
    {
      "question": "concerned chiefly or only with yourself and your advantage to the exclusion of others",
      "answer": "selfish"
    },
    {
      "question": "the document that spells out the belief system of a given church (especially the Reformation churches of the 16th century)  ",
      "answer": "confession"
    },
    {
      "question": "(chess) a piece that can be moved diagonally over unoccupied squares of the same color  ",
      "answer": "bishop"
    },
    {
      "question": "coming next after the fourth and just before the sixth in position  ",
      "answer": "fifth"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of statements or questions) charged with associative significance and often meant to mislead or influence",
      "answer": "loaded"
    },
    {
      "question": "continued in your keeping or use or memory",
      "answer": "retained"
    },
    {
      "question": "having the pinkish flush of health  ",
      "answer": "flushed"
    },
    {
      "question": "designation by the chair granting a person the right to speak in a deliberative body",
      "answer": "recognition"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a hearty manner",
      "answer": "heartily"
    },
    {
      "question": "search (an area) for prey",
      "answer": "hunt"
    },
    {
      "question": "having a face or facing especially of a specified kind or number",
      "answer": "faced"
    },
    {
      "question": "to put something (eg trust) in something",
      "answer": "repose"
    },
    {
      "question": "release from military service  ",
      "answer": "discharge"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of land) made ready for development or agriculture by clearing of trees and brush",
      "answer": "improved"
    },
    {
      "question": "having words so spaced that lines have straight even margins  ",
      "answer": "justified"
    },
    {
      "question": "white goods or clothing made with linen cloth  ",
      "answer": "linen"
    },
    {
      "question": "having the clarity and freshness of immediate experience",
      "answer": "vivid"
    },
    {
      "question": "the part of a trouser leg that provides the cloth covering for the knee  ",
      "answer": "knee"
    },
    {
      "question": "displaying effortless beauty and simplicity in movement or execution",
      "answer": "elegant"
    },
    {
      "question": "a condition superior to an earlier condition",
      "answer": "improvement"
    },
    {
      "question": "something that is certain",
      "answer": "certainty"
    },
    {
      "question": "able to make fine distinctions",
      "answer": "subtle"
    },
    {
      "question": "reveal its presence or make an appearance",
      "answer": "manifest"
    },
    {
      "question": "of a pale yellow color like straw",
      "answer": "straw"
    },
    {
      "question": "a memorial made of brass  ",
      "answer": "brass"
    },
    {
      "question": "connected with or belonging to or used in a navy",
      "answer": "naval"
    },
    {
      "question": "act in a funny or teasing way  ",
      "answer": "joke"
    },
    {
      "question": "in the lowest position",
      "answer": "lowest"
    },
    {
      "question": "occupy the whole of",
      "answer": "occupy"
    },
    {
      "question": "denoting an action or event preceding or in preparation for something more important",
      "answer": "preliminary"
    },
    {
      "question": "a custom that for a long time has been an important feature of some group or society",
      "answer": "institution"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of combining things to form a new whole  ",
      "answer": "combination"
    },
    {
      "question": "descend into or as if into some soft substance or place",
      "answer": "sink"
    },
    {
      "question": "inclined to move or be moved about",
      "answer": "floating"
    },
    {
      "question": "worthy of being chosen especially as a spouse",
      "answer": "desirable"
    },
    {
      "question": "so as to pass a given point",
      "answer": "by"
    },
    {
      "question": "preceding all others in time",
      "answer": "premier"
    },
    {
      "question": "try something new, as in order to gain experience",
      "answer": "experiment"
    },
    {
      "question": "satisfied or showing satisfaction with things as they are",
      "answer": "contented"
    },
    {
      "question": "done or made or performed with purpose and intent",
      "answer": "designed"
    },
    {
      "question": "profit from in an exploitatory manner",
      "answer": "prey"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of securities) having the owner's name entered in a register",
      "answer": "recorded"
    },
    {
      "question": "belonging to or befitting a supreme ruler",
      "answer": "imperial"
    },
    {
      "question": "make smaller",
      "answer": "contract"
    },
    {
      "question": "wear or display in an ostentatious or proud manner",
      "answer": "sport"
    },
    {
      "question": "the state of inactivity following an interruption",
      "answer": "arrest"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a vertical position",
      "answer": "upright"
    },
    {
      "question": "affected by emotion as if by electricity",
      "answer": "electric"
    },
    {
      "question": "directed up",
      "answer": "upward"
    },
    {
      "question": "protect, hide, or conceal from danger or harm  ",
      "answer": "shield"
    },
    {
      "question": "put something back where it belongs",
      "answer": "replace"
    },
    {
      "question": "of imposing height",
      "answer": "eminent"
    },
    {
      "question": "treat the body or any part of it by wrapping it, as with blankets or sheets, and applying compresses to it, or stuffing it to provide cover, containment, or therapy, or to absorb blood",
      "answer": "pack"
    },
    {
      "question": "a means of persuading or arguing",
      "answer": "weapon"
    },
    {
      "question": "with self-possession (especially in times of stress)",
      "answer": "calmly"
    },
    {
      "question": "an abstract or general idea inferred or derived from specific instances  ",
      "answer": "concept"
    },
    {
      "question": "land on a beach",
      "answer": "beach"
    },
    {
      "question": "strikingly expressive",
      "answer": "picturesque"
    },
    {
      "question": "having or conferring glory",
      "answer": "illustrious"
    },
    {
      "question": "a son of your brother or sister  ",
      "answer": "nephew"
    },
    {
      "question": "(somewhat formal) having been waked up",
      "answer": "awakened"
    },
    {
      "question": "steadfast in allegiance or duty",
      "answer": "loyal"
    },
    {
      "question": "be envious of",
      "answer": "envy"
    },
    {
      "question": "having gaps or spaces",
      "answer": "dashed"
    },
    {
      "question": "the condition of being honored (esteemed or respected or well regarded)",
      "answer": "esteem"
    },
    {
      "question": "reflect or resemble",
      "answer": "mirror"
    },
    {
      "question": "person of exceptional holiness  ",
      "answer": "saint"
    },
    {
      "question": "control of your emotions",
      "answer": "nerves"
    },
    {
      "question": "the trait of lacking restraint or control",
      "answer": "abandon"
    },
    {
      "question": "embarrassingly stingy  ",
      "answer": "cheap"
    },
    {
      "question": "a place of worship that has its own altar  ",
      "answer": "chapel"
    },
    {
      "question": "everything stated or assumed in a given discussion  ",
      "answer": "universe"
    },
    {
      "question": "having the ends united so as to form a continuous whole",
      "answer": "endless"
    },
    {
      "question": "luggage consisting of a large strong case used when traveling or for storage  ",
      "answer": "trunk"
    },
    {
      "question": "of a declining industry or technology",
      "answer": "sunset"
    },
    {
      "question": "disappointingly unsuccessful",
      "answer": "defeated"
    },
    {
      "question": "of full legal age  ",
      "answer": "major"
    },
    {
      "question": "corrupt, debase, or make impure by adding a foreign or inferior substance",
      "answer": "load"
    },
    {
      "question": "(chemistry) the ratio of the total mass of an element in the earth's crust to the total mass of the earth's crust",
      "answer": "abundance"
    },
    {
      "question": "success in mastering something difficult",
      "answer": "conquest"
    },
    {
      "question": "spur on or encourage especially by cheers and shouts",
      "answer": "cheer"
    },
    {
      "question": "quickly and without warning",
      "answer": "abruptly"
    },
    {
      "question": "changed in form or character",
      "answer": "modified"
    },
    {
      "question": "very funny",
      "answer": "killing"
    },
    {
      "question": "involving both houses of a legislature",
      "answer": "joint"
    },
    {
      "question": "arousing or provoking laughter",
      "answer": "amusing"
    },
    {
      "question": "the intended meaning of a communication  ",
      "answer": "intent"
    },
    {
      "question": "take turns working",
      "answer": "spell"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or belonging to neither the right nor the left politically or intellectually  ",
      "answer": "center"
    },
    {
      "question": "the learned profession that is mastered by graduate training in a medical school and that is devoted to preventing or alleviating or curing diseases and injuries",
      "answer": "medicine"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of convening  ",
      "answer": "convention"
    },
    {
      "question": "wealth as evidenced by sumptuous living  ",
      "answer": "luxury"
    },
    {
      "question": "express criticism towards",
      "answer": "reproach"
    },
    {
      "question": "a square piece of cloth used for wiping the eyes or nose or as a costume accessory  ",
      "answer": "handkerchief"
    },
    {
      "question": "the difference in pitch between two notes  ",
      "answer": "interval"
    },
    {
      "question": "having testicles or ovaries removed  ",
      "answer": "altered"
    },
    {
      "question": "put to death as punishment",
      "answer": "executed"
    },
    {
      "question": "having the characteristics of an acid",
      "answer": "acid"
    },
    {
      "question": "(computer science) the name given to a computer file in order to distinguish it from other files",
      "answer": "filename"
    },
    {
      "question": "provide relief for",
      "answer": "remedy"
    },
    {
      "question": "provide with drapery",
      "answer": "curtain"
    },
    {
      "question": "occurring at a convenient or suitable time",
      "answer": "favorable"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of a baseball) not hit between the foul lines  ",
      "answer": "foul"
    },
    {
      "question": "the somatic sensation of cold or heat  ",
      "answer": "temperature"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being arresting or highly emotional  ",
      "answer": "drama"
    },
    {
      "question": "having or expressing desire for something",
      "answer": "desirous"
    },
    {
      "question": "an arrangement of aerials spaced to give desired directional characteristics  ",
      "answer": "array"
    },
    {
      "question": "a score in basketball made by throwing the ball through the hoop  ",
      "answer": "basket"
    },
    {
      "question": "harmed",
      "answer": "injured"
    },
    {
      "question": "a system of means and activities whereby a social institution functions",
      "answer": "machinery"
    },
    {
      "question": "disagreeable to the senses, to the mind, or feelings ",
      "answer": "unpleasant"
    },
    {
      "question": "impossible or nearly impossible to see",
      "answer": "invisible"
    },
    {
      "question": "shrewdness as demonstrated by being skilled in deception  ",
      "answer": "craft"
    },
    {
      "question": "emitting smoke in great volume",
      "answer": "smoking"
    },
    {
      "question": "travel by canoe",
      "answer": "canoe"
    },
    {
      "question": "go through in search of something",
      "answer": "rifle"
    },
    {
      "question": "the property possessed by something or someone of outstanding importance or eminence  ",
      "answer": "greatness"
    },
    {
      "question": "very intense",
      "answer": "fiery"
    },
    {
      "question": "an army unit consisting of soldiers who fight on foot",
      "answer": "infantry"
    },
    {
      "question": "(informal to emphasize how bad it is) beyond hope of management or reform",
      "answer": "hopeless"
    },
    {
      "question": "travel by means of steam power",
      "answer": "steamer"
    },
    {
      "question": "to make the subject of dispute, contention, or litigation",
      "answer": "contest"
    },
    {
      "question": "skilled through long experience",
      "answer": "old"
    },
    {
      "question": "inform (somebody) of something",
      "answer": "advise"
    },
    {
      "question": "easily stretched",
      "answer": "stretch"
    },
    {
      "question": "asked for",
      "answer": "requested"
    },
    {
      "question": "the kind of playing that involves pressing the fingers on the strings of a stringed instrument to control the pitch",
      "answer": "stopping"
    },
    {
      "question": "treated so as to have a permanently wrinkled appearance",
      "answer": "crushed"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a prominent way",
      "answer": "prominently"
    },
    {
      "question": "outfitted or supplied with clothing",
      "answer": "suited"
    },
    {
      "question": "disposed to please",
      "answer": "amiable"
    },
    {
      "question": "work a second job, usually after hours",
      "answer": "moonlight"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or pertaining to classified information or matters affecting national security  ",
      "answer": "sensitive"
    },
    {
      "question": "not profitable or prosperous",
      "answer": "lean"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of inventing  ",
      "answer": "invention"
    },
    {
      "question": "make up",
      "answer": "coin"
    },
    {
      "question": "have certain characteristics of qualities for something",
      "answer": "lend"
    },
    {
      "question": "accept as a charge  ",
      "answer": "undertake"
    },
    {
      "question": "not agreeing with your tastes or expectations",
      "answer": "disagreeable"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause to get out",
      "answer": "retire"
    },
    {
      "question": "any loose flowing garment  ",
      "answer": "robe"
    },
    {
      "question": "write a computer program  ",
      "answer": "program"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of coming to land after a voyage  ",
      "answer": "landing"
    },
    {
      "question": "restrict or confine, \"I limit you to two visits to the pub a day\"  ",
      "answer": "limit"
    },
    {
      "question": "South American tea-like drink made from leaves of a South American holly called mate  ",
      "answer": "mate"
    },
    {
      "question": "get by special effort",
      "answer": "procure"
    },
    {
      "question": "contemptuous disregard",
      "answer": "despite"
    },
    {
      "question": "(always used with a modifier) boredom resulting from overexposure to something",
      "answer": "fatigue"
    },
    {
      "question": "containing nothing",
      "answer": "void"
    },
    {
      "question": "put before (a body)",
      "answer": "introduce"
    },
    {
      "question": "glowing or shining like fire",
      "answer": "ardent"
    },
    {
      "question": "unite musical notes by a tie  ",
      "answer": "tie"
    },
    {
      "question": "have an emotional or cognitive impact upon",
      "answer": "affect"
    },
    {
      "question": "method or manner of conduct in relation to others",
      "answer": "dealing"
    },
    {
      "question": "write for someone else",
      "answer": "ghost"
    },
    {
      "question": "a statement of taxable goods or of dutiable properties  ",
      "answer": "declaration"
    },
    {
      "question": "a deciduous tree of the genus Quercus",
      "answer": "oak"
    },
    {
      "question": "steal a base  ",
      "answer": "steal"
    },
    {
      "question": "similar especially in position or purpose",
      "answer": "corresponding"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an unexpectedly lucky way",
      "answer": "happily"
    },
    {
      "question": "affirm or avow formally or solemnly",
      "answer": "protest"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to the simultaneous performance of multiple operations",
      "answer": "parallel"
    },
    {
      "question": "engage in or perform",
      "answer": "commit"
    },
    {
      "question": "not exact",
      "answer": "inaccurate"
    },
    {
      "question": "having power to arouse interest",
      "answer": "attractive"
    },
    {
      "question": "squeeze (someone) tightly in your arms, usually with fondness",
      "answer": "embrace"
    },
    {
      "question": "uttered without voice",
      "answer": "breathed"
    },
    {
      "question": "a very fine-grained soil that is plastic when moist but hard when fired  ",
      "answer": "clay"
    },
    {
      "question": "a post made of wood  ",
      "answer": "timber"
    },
    {
      "question": "highly enthusiastic",
      "answer": "glowing"
    },
    {
      "question": "the environmental condition  ",
      "answer": "milieu"
    },
    {
      "question": "observing conventional sexual mores in speech or behavior or dress",
      "answer": "decent"
    },
    {
      "question": "something recalled to the mind  ",
      "answer": "recollection"
    },
    {
      "question": "remaining after all deductions",
      "answer": "net"
    },
    {
      "question": "the feeling that something is about to happen  ",
      "answer": "expectation"
    },
    {
      "question": "spur on",
      "answer": "encourage"
    },
    {
      "question": "move strenuously and with effort",
      "answer": "push"
    },
    {
      "question": " produce electric current by electrostatic or magnetic processes  ",
      "answer": "induce"
    },
    {
      "question": "improve one's social status",
      "answer": "climb"
    },
    {
      "question": "a cold pudding made of layers of sponge cake spread with fruit or jelly",
      "answer": "trifle"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of making a proposal",
      "answer": "proposal"
    },
    {
      "question": "not arising from natural growth or characterized by vital processes  ",
      "answer": "artificial"
    },
    {
      "question": "satisfying aesthetic standards and sensibilities",
      "answer": "artistic"
    },
    {
      "question": "recurring or reappearing from time to time",
      "answer": "periodic"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of agitating something",
      "answer": "agitation"
    },
    {
      "question": "clearly manifest",
      "answer": "frank"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who is entitled by law or by the terms of a will to inherit the estate of another  ",
      "answer": "heir"
    },
    {
      "question": "increase in quantity or bulk by adding a cheaper substance",
      "answer": "extend"
    },
    {
      "question": "during the intervening time",
      "answer": "meanwhile"
    },
    {
      "question": "a deliberately offensive act or something producing the effect of deliberate disrespect",
      "answer": "insult"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of persons) excessively affected by emotion",
      "answer": "aroused"
    },
    {
      "question": "not affected by a chemical substance (especially alcohol)  ",
      "answer": "sober"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of changing from one use or function or purpose to another  ",
      "answer": "conversion"
    },
    {
      "question": "sharply disagreeable",
      "answer": "harsh"
    },
    {
      "question": "throw or flash the light of (a lamp)",
      "answer": "shine"
    },
    {
      "question": "whip with a leather strap  ",
      "answer": "leather"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking in value or merit",
      "answer": "unworthy"
    },
    {
      "question": "exploring thoroughly  ",
      "answer": "searching"
    },
    {
      "question": "find fault with",
      "answer": "knock"
    },
    {
      "question": "powerful and effective language",
      "answer": "eloquence"
    },
    {
      "question": "sanctioned by or consistent with or operating under the law determining the fundamental political principles of a government",
      "answer": "constitutional"
    },
    {
      "question": "a downward slope or bend  ",
      "answer": "descent"
    },
    {
      "question": "keep in one's mind",
      "answer": "retain"
    },
    {
      "question": "killed unlawfully",
      "answer": "murdered"
    },
    {
      "question": "showing regard for others in manners, speech, behavior, etc.  ",
      "answer": "polite"
    },
    {
      "question": "the occupation of catching fish for a living  ",
      "answer": "fishing"
    },
    {
      "question": "a software program capable of reproducing itself and usually capable of causing great harm to files or other programs on the same computer",
      "answer": "virus"
    },
    {
      "question": "receive or obtain regularly",
      "answer": "subscribe"
    },
    {
      "question": "convert the genetic information in (a strand of DNA) into a strand of RNA, especially messenger RNA  ",
      "answer": "transcribe"
    },
    {
      "question": "hurt or upset",
      "answer": "offended"
    },
    {
      "question": "block forming a division of a hospital (or a suite of rooms) shared by patients who need a similar kind of care",
      "answer": "ward"
    },
    {
      "question": "a formal agreement establishing an association or alliance between nations or other groups to achieve a particular aim  ",
      "answer": "alliance"
    },
    {
      "question": "indicating something hard to accept",
      "answer": "bitterly"
    },
    {
      "question": "not subject to death  ",
      "answer": "immortal"
    },
    {
      "question": "provide with strings",
      "answer": "string"
    },
    {
      "question": "present in great quantity",
      "answer": "abundant"
    },
    {
      "question": "build locks in order to facilitate the navigation of vessels  ",
      "answer": "lock"
    },
    {
      "question": "limited in size or scope",
      "answer": "minor"
    },
    {
      "question": "the rhythmic arrangement of syllables  ",
      "answer": "measured"
    },
    {
      "question": "secure against future loss, damage, or liability",
      "answer": "indemnify"
    },
    {
      "question": "a wise person who is calm and rational",
      "answer": "philosopher"
    },
    {
      "question": "be at an angle",
      "answer": "slope"
    },
    {
      "question": "suffer great pains or distress  ",
      "answer": "anguish"
    },
    {
      "question": "an area within a city or town that has some distinctive features (especially one forming a community)",
      "answer": "neighborhood"
    },
    {
      "question": "come between so as to be hindrance or obstacle",
      "answer": "interfere"
    },
    {
      "question": "so extremely ugly as to be terrifying",
      "answer": "hideous"
    },
    {
      "question": "put into a good mood  ",
      "answer": "humor"
    },
    {
      "question": "exhibit on a bench",
      "answer": "bench"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being cruel and causing tension or annoyance  ",
      "answer": "cruelty"
    },
    {
      "question": "grains of common wheat",
      "answer": "wheat"
    },
    {
      "question": "alleviate or remove (pressure or stress) or make less oppressive",
      "answer": "relieve"
    },
    {
      "question": "careful and sensible",
      "answer": "prudent"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of bending something  ",
      "answer": "bending"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a formal accusation",
      "answer": "complain"
    },
    {
      "question": "make complaining remarks or noises under one's breath",
      "answer": "murmur"
    },
    {
      "question": "a sound or television recording (e.g., from a broadcast to a tape recording)  ",
      "answer": "transcription"
    },
    {
      "question": "used as a direction in music",
      "answer": "piano"
    },
    {
      "question": "wearing or provided with clothing",
      "answer": "clothed"
    },
    {
      "question": "experiencing odd bodily sensations",
      "answer": "funny"
    },
    {
      "question": "dress in a gown  ",
      "answer": "gown"
    },
    {
      "question": "consisting of two (units or components or elements or terms)",
      "answer": "binary"
    },
    {
      "question": "concerning the speaker",
      "answer": "personally"
    },
    {
      "question": "full of hardship or trials",
      "answer": "rocky"
    },
    {
      "question": "secure a vessel with an anchor",
      "answer": "anchor"
    },
    {
      "question": "a woman who runs a house of prostitution  ",
      "answer": "madam"
    },
    {
      "question": "used to express refusal or denial or disagreement etc or especially to emphasize a negative statement",
      "answer": "no"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to bodily unease that causes discomfort  ",
      "answer": "uneasy"
    },
    {
      "question": "an act of economizing",
      "answer": "economy"
    },
    {
      "question": "creation by mental activity",
      "answer": "formation"
    },
    {
      "question": "forming a right angle  ",
      "answer": "normal"
    },
    {
      "question": "cover the entire range of  ",
      "answer": "sweep"
    },
    {
      "question": "addicted to a drug  ",
      "answer": "dependent"
    },
    {
      "question": "a state or condition of being innocent of a specific crime or offense",
      "answer": "innocence"
    },
    {
      "question": "without water",
      "answer": "neat"
    },
    {
      "question": "a three-dimensional closed surface such that every point on the surface is equidistant from the center  ",
      "answer": "sphere"
    },
    {
      "question": "having help",
      "answer": "assisted"
    },
    {
      "question": "change direction",
      "answer": "bend"
    },
    {
      "question": "transmitting speech at a distance  ",
      "answer": "telephone"
    },
    {
      "question": "lifted up or set high",
      "answer": "sublime"
    },
    {
      "question": "housing for electronic instruments, as radio or television  ",
      "answer": "cabinet"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of inclining",
      "answer": "inclination"
    },
    {
      "question": "reach agreement on",
      "answer": "conclude"
    },
    {
      "question": "with sadness",
      "answer": "sadly"
    },
    {
      "question": "defectiveness or unsoundness",
      "answer": "sickness"
    },
    {
      "question": "straight-grained durable and often resinous white to yellowish timber of any of numerous trees of the genus Pinus  ",
      "answer": "pine"
    },
    {
      "question": "a crude uncouth ill-bred person lacking culture or refinement  ",
      "answer": "peasant"
    },
    {
      "question": "coat with a layer of copper  ",
      "answer": "copper"
    },
    {
      "question": "upright in position or posture",
      "answer": "erect"
    },
    {
      "question": "a line that is attached to the bow of a boat and used for tying up (as when docking or towing)  ",
      "answer": "painter"
    },
    {
      "question": "a feeling caused by uneasiness or apprehension",
      "answer": "sinking"
    },
    {
      "question": "a young woman who is the most charming and beautiful of several rivals",
      "answer": "belle"
    },
    {
      "question": "(law) a voluntary repudiation of a person's legal claim to something  ",
      "answer": "disclaimer"
    },
    {
      "question": "hunt seals  ",
      "answer": "seal"
    },
    {
      "question": "held legally responsible",
      "answer": "liable"
    },
    {
      "question": "pay close attention to",
      "answer": "heed"
    },
    {
      "question": "bear to eat",
      "answer": "stomach"
    },
    {
      "question": "distinguished from Bovidae by the male's having solid deciduous antlers  ",
      "answer": "deer"
    },
    {
      "question": "the entrance (the space in a wall) through which you enter or leave a room or building",
      "answer": "doorway"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a grave and sober manner",
      "answer": "gravely"
    },
    {
      "question": "with boldness, in a bold manner",
      "answer": "boldly"
    },
    {
      "question": "being one more than twelve  ",
      "answer": "thirteen"
    },
    {
      "question": "without reservation",
      "answer": "hearty"
    },
    {
      "question": "a message that seems to convey no meaning  ",
      "answer": "nonsense"
    },
    {
      "question": "similarity in appearance or external or superficial details  ",
      "answer": "resemblance"
    },
    {
      "question": "gather or contract into wrinkles or folds",
      "answer": "purse"
    },
    {
      "question": "the desire to have or do something that you know you should avoid",
      "answer": "temptation"
    },
    {
      "question": "damage as if by shaking or jarring",
      "answer": "disturb"
    },
    {
      "question": "change in nature, purpose, or function",
      "answer": "convert"
    },
    {
      "question": "not liable to error in judgment or action",
      "answer": "confident"
    },
    {
      "question": "prepare and supply with the necessary equipment for execution or performance",
      "answer": "mount"
    },
    {
      "question": "a variable color that is vivid red but sometimes with an orange tinge  ",
      "answer": "scarlet"
    },
    {
      "question": "adjust the spaces between words",
      "answer": "justify"
    },
    {
      "question": "saving someone or something from harm or from an unpleasant situation",
      "answer": "salvation"
    },
    {
      "question": "carry luggage or supplies",
      "answer": "porter"
    },
    {
      "question": "have or feel a dislike or distaste for",
      "answer": "dislike"
    },
    {
      "question": "consisting of or made up of bone",
      "answer": "bone"
    },
    {
      "question": "a casual meeting with a person or thing  ",
      "answer": "encounter"
    },
    {
      "question": "the ability to recall past occurrences  ",
      "answer": "remembrance"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of filling something  ",
      "answer": "filling"
    },
    {
      "question": "fight with fencing swords  ",
      "answer": "fence"
    },
    {
      "question": "obvious to the eye or mind",
      "answer": "conspicuous"
    },
    {
      "question": "scope for freedom of e.g. action or thought",
      "answer": "latitude"
    },
    {
      "question": "a marvellous event manifesting a supernatural act of a divine agent  ",
      "answer": "miracle"
    },
    {
      "question": "in place of, or as an alternative to",
      "answer": "alternatively"
    },
    {
      "question": "touch or rub constantly",
      "answer": "worry"
    },
    {
      "question": "a matching set of furniture  ",
      "answer": "suite"
    },
    {
      "question": "an officer holding a commissioned rank in the United States Navy or the United States Coast Guard",
      "answer": "lieutenant"
    },
    {
      "question": "describe roughly or briefly or give the main points or summary of",
      "answer": "sketch"
    },
    {
      "question": "killing someone by gunfire",
      "answer": "shooting"
    },
    {
      "question": "a condition of decline following successes",
      "answer": "twilight"
    },
    {
      "question": "a meeting devoted to a particular activity",
      "answer": "session"
    },
    {
      "question": "to form the comparative or superlative form on an adjective or adverb  ",
      "answer": "compare"
    },
    {
      "question": "a child's four-wheeled toy cart sometimes used for coasting  ",
      "answer": "wagon"
    },
    {
      "question": "so as to leave much space or distance between",
      "answer": "widely"
    },
    {
      "question": "continue in existence after (an adversity, etc.)",
      "answer": "survive"
    },
    {
      "question": "showing or motivated by sympathy and understanding and generosity",
      "answer": "charitable"
    },
    {
      "question": "a distinguishing emblem",
      "answer": "colors"
    },
    {
      "question": "morally excellent  ",
      "answer": "virtuous"
    },
    {
      "question": "extreme in degree or extent or amount or impact",
      "answer": "frightful"
    },
    {
      "question": "patronized by  ",
      "answer": "fashionable"
    },
    {
      "question": "with honesty",
      "answer": "rightly"
    },
    {
      "question": "excluded from use or mention",
      "answer": "forbidden"
    },
    {
      "question": "a form of government whose head of state is not a monarch",
      "answer": "republic"
    },
    {
      "question": "worthy of being honored",
      "answer": "honorable"
    },
    {
      "question": "(especially of the face) reddened or suffused with or as if with blood from emotion or exertion",
      "answer": "crimson"
    },
    {
      "question": "maintained at length without interruption or weakening",
      "answer": "sustained"
    },
    {
      "question": "replying",
      "answer": "answering"
    },
    {
      "question": "prepare (a metal) for soldering or brazing by applying a thin layer of solder to the surface  ",
      "answer": "tin"
    },
    {
      "question": "lie adjacent to another or share a boundary",
      "answer": "border"
    },
    {
      "question": "in spite of contrary volition  ",
      "answer": "unwilling"
    },
    {
      "question": "take liberties or act with too much confidence  ",
      "answer": "presume"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of undissolved particles in a fluid) supported or kept from sinking or falling by buoyancy and without apparent attachment",
      "answer": "suspended"
    },
    {
      "question": "an engagement fought between two military forces  ",
      "answer": "combat"
    },
    {
      "question": "a protective covering that protects the outside of a building  ",
      "answer": "facing"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a violent manner",
      "answer": "violently"
    },
    {
      "question": "acceptable as a deduction (especially as a tax deduction)  ",
      "answer": "deductible"
    },
    {
      "question": "patterned with alternating squares of color  ",
      "answer": "checked"
    },
    {
      "question": "having control over urination and defecation  ",
      "answer": "continent"
    },
    {
      "question": "convert (plant material) into hay  ",
      "answer": "hay"
    },
    {
      "question": "narrow recessed balcony area along an upper floor on the interior of a building",
      "answer": "gallery"
    },
    {
      "question": "providing knowledge",
      "answer": "educational"
    },
    {
      "question": "a room used primarily for sleeping  ",
      "answer": "bedroom"
    },
    {
      "question": "toward the center or interior",
      "answer": "inward"
    },
    {
      "question": "the practice of being unjust or unfair  ",
      "answer": "injustice"
    },
    {
      "question": "contemptibly narrow in outlook",
      "answer": "petty"
    },
    {
      "question": "keep engaged",
      "answer": "engage"
    },
    {
      "question": "cut a groove into",
      "answer": "chase"
    },
    {
      "question": "appear briefly",
      "answer": "gleam"
    },
    {
      "question": "a courteous manner  ",
      "answer": "courtesy"
    },
    {
      "question": "done with very great haste and without due deliberation",
      "answer": "hasty"
    },
    {
      "question": "the state of being unsullied by sin or moral wrong",
      "answer": "purity"
    },
    {
      "question": "organized opposition to authority",
      "answer": "rebellion"
    },
    {
      "question": "marked by refinement in taste and manners",
      "answer": "civilized"
    },
    {
      "question": "regard as objective  ",
      "answer": "project"
    },
    {
      "question": "preparing or putting through a prescribed procedure",
      "answer": "processing"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of pausing uncertainly",
      "answer": "hesitation"
    },
    {
      "question": "maneuver a vehicle into a parking space",
      "answer": "park"
    },
    {
      "question": "having or bringing good fortune",
      "answer": "lucky"
    },
    {
      "question": "a dislike of anything that causes delay  ",
      "answer": "impatience"
    },
    {
      "question": "subjected to a penalty (as pain or shame or restraint or loss) for an offense or fault or in order to coerce some behavior (as a confession or obedience)  ",
      "answer": "punished"
    },
    {
      "question": "have or establish a relationship to",
      "answer": "relate"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being probable",
      "answer": "probability"
    },
    {
      "question": "the property of tasting as if it contains sugar  ",
      "answer": "sweetness"
    },
    {
      "question": "having services engaged for a fee",
      "answer": "hired"
    },
    {
      "question": "take forcibly from legal custody",
      "answer": "rescue"
    },
    {
      "question": "changed in order to improve or made more fit for a particular purpose",
      "answer": "adapted"
    },
    {
      "question": "concerning or belonging to all or at least two or more nations",
      "answer": "international"
    },
    {
      "question": "in Christianity, clergymen collectively (as distinguished from the laity)  ",
      "answer": "clergy"
    },
    {
      "question": "prudent",
      "answer": "guarded"
    },
    {
      "question": "the activity of making visits",
      "answer": "visiting"
    },
    {
      "question": "unrestrained excitement or enthusiasm",
      "answer": "madness"
    },
    {
      "question": "the ultimate agency regarded as predetermining the course of events (often personified as a woman)",
      "answer": "destiny"
    },
    {
      "question": "changed for (replaced by) something different  ",
      "answer": "exchanged"
    },
    {
      "question": "suitable for a particular person or place or condition etc",
      "answer": "appropriate"
    },
    {
      "question": "exciting strong but not unpleasant emotions",
      "answer": "stirring"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who speaks by divine inspiration",
      "answer": "prophet"
    },
    {
      "question": "direct the flow of",
      "answer": "channel"
    },
    {
      "question": "an instrument or machine that is used in warfare, such as a battering ram, catapult, artillery piece, etc.",
      "answer": "engine"
    },
    {
      "question": "a landowner who leases to others  ",
      "answer": "landlord"
    },
    {
      "question": "unusually or exceptionally",
      "answer": "extra"
    },
    {
      "question": "(theater) the space over the stage (out of view of the audience) used to store scenery (drop curtains)  ",
      "answer": "flies"
    },
    {
      "question": "coat with beaten egg",
      "answer": "egg"
    },
    {
      "question": "payment by one nation for protection by another  ",
      "answer": "tribute"
    },
    {
      "question": "the state of being of noble birth  ",
      "answer": "nobility"
    },
    {
      "question": "influence (somebody's) opinion in advance  ",
      "answer": "prejudice"
    },
    {
      "question": "reach full flavor by absorbing air and being let to stand after having been uncorked",
      "answer": "breathe"
    },
    {
      "question": "pass through or into",
      "answer": "thread"
    },
    {
      "question": "packed closely together",
      "answer": "tight"
    },
    {
      "question": "towards the shore from the water",
      "answer": "ashore"
    },
    {
      "question": "not charged with a bullet",
      "answer": "blank"
    },
    {
      "question": "the rays of the sun",
      "answer": "sunlight"
    },
    {
      "question": "furnish with costumes",
      "answer": "costume"
    },
    {
      "question": "causing surprise or wonder or amazement",
      "answer": "surprising"
    },
    {
      "question": "immoderation as a consequence of going beyond sufficient or permitted limits  ",
      "answer": "excess"
    },
    {
      "question": "sieve so that it becomes the consistency of rice",
      "answer": "rice"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a special manner",
      "answer": "specially"
    },
    {
      "question": "coming down freely under the influence of gravity",
      "answer": "dropping"
    },
    {
      "question": "with relatively high volume",
      "answer": "loudly"
    },
    {
      "question": "performs some wicked deed  ",
      "answer": "wretch"
    },
    {
      "question": "understood in a certain way",
      "answer": "interpreted"
    },
    {
      "question": "a garment made of the dressed hairy coat of a mammal  ",
      "answer": "fur"
    },
    {
      "question": "either the outer margin or the inner margin of the aperture of a gastropod's shell  ",
      "answer": "lip"
    },
    {
      "question": "a service that an organization or a piece of equipment offers you",
      "answer": "facility"
    },
    {
      "question": "devoted to a cause or ideal or purpose",
      "answer": "dedicated"
    },
    {
      "question": "provided with or as if with a crown or a crown as specified",
      "answer": "crowned"
    },
    {
      "question": "(ecology) a group of organisms (plants and animals) that live together in a certain geographical region and constitute a community with a few dominant species  ",
      "answer": "association"
    },
    {
      "question": "in the current fashion or style  ",
      "answer": "latest"
    },
    {
      "question": "a crucial stage or turning point in the course of something",
      "answer": "crisis"
    },
    {
      "question": "a community of people in a religious order (especially nuns) living together  ",
      "answer": "convent"
    },
    {
      "question": "a moralistic rebuke",
      "answer": "sermon"
    },
    {
      "question": "confidently declared to be so",
      "answer": "asserted"
    },
    {
      "question": "a small being, human in form, playful and having magical powers  ",
      "answer": "fairy"
    },
    {
      "question": "subject to torture",
      "answer": "torture"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a telephone call or mail a package so that the recipient pays",
      "answer": "collect"
    },
    {
      "question": "capable of independent and apparently intelligent action",
      "answer": "smart"
    },
    {
      "question": "unable to speak because of hereditary deafness  ",
      "answer": "dumb"
    },
    {
      "question": "make attractive or acceptable",
      "answer": "recommend"
    },
    {
      "question": "increase the value of",
      "answer": "appreciate"
    },
    {
      "question": "showing effects of planning or manipulation",
      "answer": "contrived"
    },
    {
      "question": "an undeveloped field of study",
      "answer": "frontier"
    },
    {
      "question": "so as to be positive",
      "answer": "positively"
    },
    {
      "question": "assert to be true",
      "answer": "insist"
    },
    {
      "question": "arousing to a particular emotion or action  ",
      "answer": "inspiration"
    },
    {
      "question": "a headlong jump (or fall)",
      "answer": "header"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of making or enacting laws  ",
      "answer": "legislation"
    },
    {
      "question": "a disorderly crowd of people  ",
      "answer": "mob"
    },
    {
      "question": "resembling velvet in having a smooth soft surface  ",
      "answer": "velvet"
    },
    {
      "question": "the departure of a vessel from a port  ",
      "answer": "sailing"
    },
    {
      "question": "with respect to the mind",
      "answer": "upstairs"
    },
    {
      "question": "the property of having a harsh unpleasant taste  ",
      "answer": "bitterness"
    },
    {
      "question": "put a shirt on  ",
      "answer": "shirt"
    },
    {
      "question": "selected as the best",
      "answer": "elect"
    },
    {
      "question": "become unfit for consumption or use",
      "answer": "spoil"
    },
    {
      "question": "in bodily form",
      "answer": "bodily"
    },
    {
      "question": "remorse caused by feeling responsible for some offense  ",
      "answer": "guilt"
    },
    {
      "question": "exceedingly bad",
      "answer": "horrid"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a manner or order or direction the reverse of normal",
      "answer": "backward"
    },
    {
      "question": "take into one's family",
      "answer": "adopt"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who is a member of the faculty at a college or university  ",
      "answer": "professor"
    },
    {
      "question": "furnish money for",
      "answer": "fund"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking training or experience",
      "answer": "raw"
    },
    {
      "question": "concern with the distinction between good and evil or right and wrong",
      "answer": "morality"
    },
    {
      "question": "slightly wet",
      "answer": "damp"
    },
    {
      "question": "a golf club (a wood) with a near vertical face that is used for hitting long shots from the tee  ",
      "answer": "driver"
    },
    {
      "question": "without the natural or usual covering",
      "answer": "bald"
    },
    {
      "question": "prominently forward",
      "answer": "foremost"
    },
    {
      "question": "gymnastic apparatus consisting of a pair of heavy metal circles (usually covered with leather) suspended by ropes",
      "answer": "rings"
    },
    {
      "question": "socially uncomfortable",
      "answer": "awkward"
    },
    {
      "question": "(French) a street or road in France  ",
      "answer": "rue"
    },
    {
      "question": "violating principles of justice",
      "answer": "unjust"
    },
    {
      "question": "displaying a sense of being better than others",
      "answer": "superiority"
    },
    {
      "question": "marked by complexity and richness of detail",
      "answer": "elaborate"
    },
    {
      "question": "being ten more than sixty  ",
      "answer": "seventy"
    },
    {
      "question": "inquire into",
      "answer": "research"
    },
    {
      "question": "(intensifier before a figurative expression) without exaggeration",
      "answer": "literally"
    },
    {
      "question": "discretion in practical affairs  ",
      "answer": "prudence"
    },
    {
      "question": "do landscape gardening",
      "answer": "landscape"
    },
    {
      "question": "breathing laboriously or convulsively  ",
      "answer": "blown"
    },
    {
      "question": "deliver a lecture or talk",
      "answer": "lecture"
    },
    {
      "question": "feel happiness or joy  ",
      "answer": "rejoice"
    },
    {
      "question": "not necessary  ",
      "answer": "unnecessary"
    },
    {
      "question": "form into a ridge  ",
      "answer": "ridge"
    },
    {
      "question": "an individual quantity of food or drink taken as part of a meal",
      "answer": "helping"
    },
    {
      "question": "intense mournfulness  ",
      "answer": "woe"
    },
    {
      "question": "achieve a point or goal",
      "answer": "have"
    },
    {
      "question": "a feeling of craving something",
      "answer": "appetite"
    },
    {
      "question": "slow to learn or understand",
      "answer": "dense"
    },
    {
      "question": "give evidence of the quality of",
      "answer": "reflect"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause someone to believe an untruth",
      "answer": "deceive"
    }
  ]
}